that the first thing you have to find is an
open space, a space where it can
be controlled, lighting a
fire, not the fire, you always have to
look for it to be  controlled that it is not a
huge bonfire, if it is going to be a
huge bonfire, look for a much more
open space. Here I am between several trees.
The truth is that I do not see any risk. I
have the closest tree more than two meters
away from where the fire is going to be.  fire
and also clean the entire area the entire
area that also around the
stones I was already cleaning it I was
dragging it with my foot removing all the
possible tinder that could be ignited that
the match was the game in addition to
this I was previously hitting it with the with the
shovel climbing a small hole
to be able to reach the earth below
where the earth is all the
organic matter the truth is that it is very
complicated for it to catch fire it is very easy
for it to catch fire everything is on the
surface everything removes everything that
is around
So the truth is that it is the
safest way you can do it. The
other thing is also very important to
find stones. The stones are a
natural insulator for the town but they are not
going to learn, they are not going to heat up and they are not
going to pass the test.  sufficient amount of heat
to light something else that
you have the capacity to be able to isolate
where you are going to have the fire from the outside
is the best you can do then
the stones you can always find you can't
always find and you can see the
way to be able to get stones
first delete  Chunga Sacoyo
and another thing that is very important,
normally when you are in the mountains
making a fire, it is to warm up so you
can cook, but if it is to warm
you, something very good that you can do is
make a heat reflector. When
you make a fire, the heat goes towards you.
everywhere, if you
put a wall somewhere, that is what I have here,
and I will show you in a moment, what
you are going to achieve is being able to reflect the
heat where you want. I am